{
    "subject": "resource/1995\u201396_Liverpool_F.C._season",
    "predicate": "property/team",
    "object": "resource/Liverpool_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "The team of the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season is Liverpool F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870343804359436,
            "question": "Who were the members of the Liverpool F.C. team during the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9683833122253418,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the Liverpool F.C. team from the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8827800750732422,
            "question": "Which year did the Liverpool F.C. team play during that season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8307029604911804,
            "question": "What team did the players of the 1995-96 season belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810670018196106,
            "question": "What was the name of the football club during the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4176465570926666,
            "question": "Who comprised the team during that season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2513887882232666,
            "question": "Is there information about the players who were part of this team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1513494998216629,
            "question": "What is the name of the football club mentioned in this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14003755152225494,
            "question": "In what sport did the players of this team compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13605763018131256,
            "question": "What season are we talking about in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team of the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season is Liverpool F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8210_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what sport did the players of this team compete?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8210_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the football club mentioned in this statement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8210_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there information about the players who were part of this team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8210_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8210_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**: They actually finished eleventh in the table, a far cry from the optimism that began the season with them being challenging for the title."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Yes, the team in question for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was indeed Liverpool F.C."
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season refers to a specific season of the team, whereas the statement claims that the \"team\" of that season is the same as the team itself (Liverpool F.C.), which is a tautology and doesn't provide any meaningful information.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}